moneyhomeblog.com 2017-09-11

# Privacy Policy

The Privacy Policy of our visitors to **http://www.moneyhomeblog.com** is important to us.

At **http://www.moneyhomeblog.com** , we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit **http://www.moneyhomeblog.com** , and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

##  **Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

##  **Cookies and Web Beacons**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

## Adds

We also use third party advertisements on **http://www.moneyhomeblog.com** to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

##  **DoubleClick DART cookies**

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (“interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting [http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx ](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx)

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

## Affiliate Links

W sometimes use affiliate links on this site, but our opinion is not for sale. Every affiliate link we share is for a product we find useful. Please always do your own research before making any purchase online.

To keep all the content of my blog free, we may be compensated from time to time. Any income goes straight back into the website to pay costs associated with running a business, including hosting fees, blog design, and my own time.

Our opinion & my integrity is paramount. We will never recommend something to you that we believe has no value.

Posts may contain affiliate links. Purchasing through them helps support this blog. Clicking on an affiliate link or signing up for a service or ordering a product may be earning me a commission which helps to keep this blog going.

Affiliates:

## Contact

If you have any concerns about this policy, please feel free to email us.

The following two tabs change content below.

  * Bio
  * Latest Posts

I Am Frank Joseph - I work fully online, building businesses online is my passion. If you want to learn from me, please read the FREE ebook ‘How to Make Money Online and Get Rich’: (just click my name)
